[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sugar is important for the proper function of which of these bodily systems?", "correct_answer": "Nervous system", "incorrect_answers": ["Cardiovascular system", "Endocrine system", "Digestive system"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the ex-presidents gets killed in the final bank robbery in Point Break?", "correct_answer": "Lyndon B. Johnson", "incorrect_answers": ["Jimmy Carter", "Ronald Reagan", "Richard Nixon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The cat family featured in The Aristocats stay the night in a house containing a band of cats. What is the name of the lead cat in the group?", "correct_answer": "Scat Cat", "incorrect_answers": ["Hit Cat", "Top Cat", "Billy Bass"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 1991 film The Silence of the Lambs?", "correct_answer": "Jonathan Demme", "incorrect_answers": ["Roman Polanski", "Joel Coen", "Steven Spielberg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture for 1982 was awarded to this movie.", "correct_answer": "Inchon", "incorrect_answers": ["Annie", "Butterfly", "The Pirate Movie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie St. Elmos Fire, during the night Billy fights Felicias husband, his shirt is covered with images of what creature?", "correct_answer": "bats", "incorrect_answers": ["dinosaurs", "turtles", "lizards"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the capital city of the U.S. state of Washington.", "correct_answer": "Olympia", "incorrect_answers": ["Seattle", "Madison", "Boise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these songs by Aaliyah was included in the soundtrack of the 2000 movie Romeo Must Die?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Try Again", "Are You Feelin Me?", "I Dont Wanna"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Out of 200 vampire bats, approximately how many have rabies?", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "25", "10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Blonde hair was important to Hitler, according to him it symbolized this.", "correct_answer": "The purity of the Aryan race", "incorrect_answers": ["Valor", "German nationality", "Innocence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Trilobites developed one of the first complex visual systems.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does SYS mean when used in instant messaging ?", "correct_answer": "see you soon", "incorrect_answers": ["still your spouse", "see your sister", "system is down"]}]